{
    "subject": "resource/Aaron_Ramsey",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1990-12-26",
    "human_readable": "Aaron Ramsey was born on December 26, 1990.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.944407045841217,
            "question": "December 26th of which year marks Aaron Ramsey's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8829343914985657,
            "question": "When was Aaron Ramsey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8328952789306641,
            "question": "What day was Aaron Ramsey born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045788407325745,
            "question": "Is Aaron Ramsey a December baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8018004894256592,
            "question": "How old was Aaron Ramsey on December 26th, 2022?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7790452241897583,
            "question": "What is Aaron Ramsey's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6567732691764832,
            "question": "What month and day was Aaron Ramsey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4171491861343384,
            "question": "If today is January 1st, 2024, how old would Aaron Ramsey be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4104168117046356,
            "question": "In what year did Aaron Ramsey come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3797655701637268,
            "question": "Calculate Aaron Ramsey's age as of today."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Aaron Ramsey was born on December 26, 1990.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9311_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Aaron Ramsey come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9311_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is January 1st, 2024, how old would Aaron Ramsey be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9311_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was Aaron Ramsey born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9311_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9311_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Aaron Ramsey's birthdate as December 26, 1990. There are multiple documents confirming this fact, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9311/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9311/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9311/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt, and others. Therefore, the triple is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents consistently state that Aaron Ramsey was born on December 26, 1990. Each relevant document provided includes this birth date information, confirming the query's accuracy based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}